https://www.steelbuilding.com/privacy/

Skip To Main Content
I Have some questions. Please give me a call.
Home / Terms of Use & Privacy Statement
Terms of Use & Privacy Statement
Effective Date:
June 1, 2020
This
Online Privacy Policy applies to information about you that SteelBuilding.com,
LLC, part of the Cornerstone Building Brands family (“SteelBuilding.com,” “we,”
“our,” “us”) may obtain when you visit SteelBuilding.com (the “Site”). This
Privacy Policy describes how we may collect, use, or share information about
you; your choices regarding our use of your information; how we safeguard such
information; and how you may contact us regarding our privacy practices.
Collection of Personal Information
Information
you provide. We may obtain information that you provide
directly to us when you interact with the Site (e.g., when you request a
quote). This information may include personal
information, which is information that can be used to identify you
individually, such as your name, home zip code, email address, and phone
number.
Information
collected automatically. In addition to information that you submit to
us, we may collect certain information automatically using various tools and
technologies such as cookies and web server logs. The types of information we
collect may include IP addresses, device identifiers, browser characteristics,
operating system details, language preferences, referring URLs, length of
visits, and pages viewed. A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send
to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag
that identifies your computer but not you. Many web browsers are set to accept
cookies by default, but you may be able to set your browser to notify you
before you receive a cookie, or to remove or reject cookies. Please note that
if you disable cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of this
Site or other websites and that disabling cookies may invalidate opt outs that
rely on cookies to function.
Your web browser may have settings that allow
you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal when you visit various websites or use
online services. Like many websites, this Site is not designed to respond to
“Do Not Track” signals received from browsers. To learn more about “Do Not
Track” signals, you may wish to visit www.allaboutdnt.com.
Use of Personal Information
We may use personal information we
collect through the Site to:
Facilitate and personalize your
user experience;
Conduct statistical analysis of
Site content, layout, and features for our marketing purposes;
Improve the Site, our marketing, or
services we may offer;
Communicate with you, including to
respond to your requests or inquiries;
Deliver promotional content to you;
Send you newsletters;
Comply with applicable laws, regulations,
or legal process, as well as industry standards and our company policies;
Prevent, investigate, identify,
stop, or take any other action with regard to suspected or actual
fraudulent or illegal activity, or any activity that violates our policies;
or
For any other purpose, with your
consent.
Sharing of Personal Information
We may share your personal information with our
parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, business partners, and vendors that provide
services on our behalf. These parties are not meant to use personal information
except for the purpose(s) for which it was provided.
In the event of a business transaction, such as
if we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (e.g.,
further to a merger, reorganization, liquidation, or any other business
transaction, including negotiations of such transactions), we reserve the right
to disclose any information we obtain through the Site. You acknowledge that
such transfers may occur and are permitted by and subject to this Privacy
Policy.
Additionally, we may disclose information when
required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal processes, or in response
to activities that are unlawful or a violation of our rules for use of the
Site, or to protect and defend our rights
or property.
Security
We take reasonable measures to protect your
information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure,
alteration, and destruction. Nevertheless, transmission via the Internet and
online digital storage are not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the
security of your information collected through the Site.
Third-Party Analytics
and Advertising
We may use third-party technology to collect and
use data in connection with interest-based advertising, and other parties may
collect your personal information about your online activities over time and
across different devices and online properties when you use the Site. These ad
technology companies and advertisers may use, store, or access cookies, web
beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from
the Site and elsewhere on the Internet and use that information to provide
advertising services to us, including interest-based advertising or
advertisements targeted to your interests delivered over time and across online
services and devices.
We may use certain web analytics services,
including Google Analytics, to help us understand and analyze how visitors use
the Site and to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. We’ve implemented
Google Analytics Advertising Features such as remarketing with analytics,
interest-based advertising, demographics and interests reporting, and user
segment analysis. We and our vendors may use first-party cookies or other
first-party identifiers as well as third-party cookies or other third-party
identifiers to deliver advertisements, create a profile of you, measure your
interests, detect your demographics, detect your location, and personalize
content.
To
find out more about how these analytics services manage the privacy of
information in conjunction with delivering ads online and how to opt out of
information collection by these networks, visit www.youradchoices.com and www.networkadvertising.org.
For
more information on how Google Analytics uses data collected through the Site,
visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners. To opt out of Google Analytics cookies, visit adssettings.google.com and tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Please note that SteelBuilding.com does not
control how other parties manage their opt-out processes.
Linked Websites
The Site may include links to websites that are
not owned or operated by SteelBuilding.com. This Privacy Policy does not apply
to those websites, which may have their own privacy policies or notices that
you should review to understand how they may use or disclose your personal
information. SteelBuilding.com is not responsible for the content or privacy
practices of any linked websites that it does not control. Any personal
information you submit through these websites is governed by the third-party
service provider’s own privacy policy and terms and conditions.
The Site may also provide links to websites
operated by SteelBuilding.com, our parent, brands, affiliates, or subsidiaries.
Unless indicated otherwise, these websites are not governed by this Privacy
Policy. For information on how these websites may collect, use, or disclose
your personal information, we encourage you to review the privacy policies
posted on the linked websites.
Information for California Residents
California’s “Shine the Light” Law. California law permits customers in California
to request certain details about how their personal information is shared with
third parties and, in some cases, affiliates if that personal information is
shared for those third parties’ and affiliates’ own direct marketing purposes.
We do not share personal information with third parties or affiliates for those
third parties’ or affiliates’ own direct marketing purposes. Californians may
request information about our compliance with this law by emailing us at privacy@cornerstone-bb.com
or
mailing to Cornerstone Building Brands, Inc., Attention: Data Privacy, 10943
North Sam Houston Pkwy W, Houston, Texas, 77064.
To
make a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if
this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident, and
provide your current California address to which we will send our response.
Your inquiry must specify “California Privacy Rights Request” in the subject
line of the email or the first line of the letter and include your name, street
address, city, state, and ZIP code. Please note that we are only required to
respond to one request per customer each year.
California Consumer Privacy Act. The California Consumer Privacy Act
(the “CCPA”), which provides California consumers certain rights regarding
their personal information (“PI”), became effective on January 1, 2020. As of
that date, the California Attorney General had not completed the rulemaking process
to establish the regulations for covered businesses to implement the law.
Accordingly, we may update information in this section regarding our data
practices and your rights under the CCPA, modify our methods for responding to
your requests, and/or supplement our responses to your requests as we continue
to develop our compliance program to reflect the development of the law and our
understanding of how it relates to our data practices.
If you are a California consumer and
would like to make a request pursuant to your “right to know about personal
information collected, disclosed or sold” (including your right to obtain
copies of specific pieces of PI), your “right to request deletion of personal
information,” or your “right to opt-out of the sale of personal information,”
you may contact us at privacy@cornerstone-bb.com or complete and submit the form, here. We will respond to your request as
soon as we have guidance on how to properly verify your identity and the
appropriate response parameters.
Please note that CCPA rights do not
apply to PI collected from (1) job applicants, current and former employees, or
independent contractors; or (2) representatives of another business in
connection with business communications or transactions.
Examples of the types of PI we may
collect from California consumers, and of the purposes for such collection, are
outlined in the chart below.
Category
of PI
Examples
Purpose(s)
Identifiers
Name, physical address, phone
number, Internet Protocol address, email address, unique personal
identification number
Processing transactions,
customizing concurrent consumer experiences, detecting fraud, security,
marketing
Customer / Personal Records
Name, physical address, phone
number, email address, payment card details, employment information
Processing transactions,
customizing concurrent consumer experiences, detecting fraud, security,
Browsing history, search history,
information regarding interactions with our website or advertisements
Employment-related information,
such as business contact details
Facilitating transactions
We will revise this section as the
law becomes clearer and we are able to provide you with more specific
information about your CCPA rights and how to exercise them.
Please
note that “Shine the Light” rights and CCPA rights are established under
different legal regimes and must be exercised separately.
Information for Users Outside the United States
If you are visiting the Site from outside the
United States, please be aware that information we obtain about you will be
processed in the United States or in other jurisdictions. By using the Site,
you acknowledge and consent to the international transfer and processing of
your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy. Please be aware that
the data protection laws and regulations that apply to your personal data
transferred to the United States or other countries may be different from the
laws in your country of residence.
Revisions
This Privacy Policy is subject to change
at our discretion. We will indicate changes, including material changes, to the
Privacy Policy by updating the “Effective Date” at the top of this page. Your
continued use of this Site after any update to this Privacy Policy will
constitute your acceptance of the changes.
Contact Information
You may direct comments or questions regarding
this Privacy Policy via email to privacy@cornerstone-bb.com.
